pearlacademy.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy « Pearl Academy

Download our mobile app[](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.pearlacademy.PearlAcademy2014)

Announcement: Admissions Open - Diploma and Professional Diploma Programmes 

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

###### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. 

###### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. We do not share aggregate cookie and tracking information with third parties. 

###### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when:

  * Permitted or required by law; or 
  * Trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions
  * Investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

###### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
